Bui Bang Vu (Fresher)

Mobile (+84) 329 524 889

Email vu.bb180396@gmail.com

Date of birth 18/03/1996

Address Thai Ha str, Dong Da dist, Ha Noi

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/chrisbui9966/



OBJECTIVE

Detail-oriented individual eager to work as a Data Analyst position, where I can put my abilities and skills to the best use possible: conduct thorough research where necessary; good command of English; and diverse knowledge about my own nation through many years of studying in northern, central and southern Vietnam. Devoted to continuing professional growth through training.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Key DRM Monitor

- Statistics of DRM key (Digital Rights Management Key) and usage to provide a reasonable budget.
- Excel, SQL Server (<u>DRM Link</u>)

Customer 360 Project

- Use data based on existing customer behavior to predict growth and lose based on RFM analyst.
- Excel, SQL Server, PowerBI (RFM Link)

Uniace SEO Analytics

- Evaluate the effectiveness of digital marketing campaigns on website uniace.vn.
- Excel, SQL Server, PowerBI (<u>Uniace SEO Link</u>)

E-Commerce Discount Campain

• Write an analysis to find out the top three sellers and buyers who abuse the program. Excel, Python (<u>E-Commerce Link</u>)

SKILLS

MS Excel	Pivot Table, VBA
MS SQL Server	Proficient in using basic, intermediate commands
PowerBI, Tableau	Data Visualization, DAX, Manipulating data
Python	Proficient in matplotlib, pandas, numpy

CERTIFICATES

Apr 2023	Google Data Analytics
Mar 2023	Hackerrank SQL Intermediate Certificate

EDUCATION

	Ho Chi Minh University of Technology and Education
Oct 2014 - Jan 2019	Major: Mechatronics
	Bachelor Degree: Good

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fer 2022 - Jan 2023

VI CAMERA CO., LTD

Aftersales Leader

- Use ODOO for managing and tracking current stock levels.
- Coordinate with technicians to make statistics of fault status and plan to handle and report to manager.
- Statisticize warranty claims for the manufacturer.

Jun 2020 - Jan 2022

SHENZHEN GROWATT NEW ENERGY

Service Engineer

Responsibilities:

- Work on Growatt OSS (Online Smart Service) to monitor Inverter parameter and predict risk of Photovoltaic Systems.
- Provide on-site support for project customers, use tools and software for testing and evaluating the Photovoltaic system.
- Report spare parts inventory to Head Quater.

Performances:

- Collect error data from server about Inverter 8K one phase to improve Inverter hardware.
- Use Excel to build the spare parts management file and summarize the status of the distributor's faulty inverter.

Dec 2018 - Mar 2020

DECATHLON VIETNAM

Quality Production Leader

Responsibilities:

- Control the Quality of the Products in line and before shipment.
- Support & cooperate with the Factory team to improve Quality System.
- Summarize defects data to control, standardize issues by image and number.

Performances:

- Build a Procedure to control Products in line and before shipment.
- Decrease Blocking Rate from 33% to under 5% by collect data inline.

REFERENCES

Mr. Tran Hoang Long | Data Analyst | FPT Telecom